vitaleboutique.it 2018-09-02

# Privacy Vitale

**Vitale Srl-Privacy Online**

By accessing the website [www.vitaleboutique.it operated by](http://www.vitaleboutique.it/) Vitale Srl or using its content, you accept the terms of this Online Privacy policy, as detailed below. If you do not accept these terms, please do not access the site and not to use its contents.

Collection of personal information

As you perform activities such as ordering products, downloading software, or participate in contests, Vitale Srl may ask you to provide personal information by compiling and sending a specific form (e-form). You are totally free to accept or decline this request. If you decide to accept Vitale Srl may ask you to provide personal and/or corporate information and other data that identifies you.

Vitale Srl collects this information to register it and allow you to participate in activities chosen by you. If you order a product, for example, the information is used to send the goods or other benefits that may be offered to registered users.

Vitale Srl will use the information you provided to keep you updated on new initiatives, special offers and other new products and services of Vitale Srl.

Vitale Srl recognizes and attaches great value to a responsible use of such information.

Vitale Srl will adhere scrupulously to your specifications.

Use of cookies and the types of data processed

Visiting our. [www.vitaleboutique.it site, you can move](http://www.vitaleboutique.it/) between pages anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we use "cookies" to keep track of your passage. A cookie is a reduced set of data transferred to your browser from a Web server and can only be read by the server that made the transfer.

_This category of data includes:_

•    the IP addresses of computers used by users who use the service;

•    the number of hits;

•    pages viewed;

•    the date and time that you access;

•    delia's life on the content displayed.

•    the page of origin before arriving at [www.VostraDitta.com](http://www.vostraditta.com/)

•    the Web browser;

•    the operating system you are using.

•    the resolution of the system used.

•    The language

•    The destination

The data is used for the purpose of obtaining anonymous statistical information on site usage and to check its correct functioning. The data could be used to ascertain responsibility in case of hypothetical computer crimes against the site except for this possibility, the data on web contacts do not persist for more than seven days. No data is disclosed.

Almost all browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can have your browser notify you when you receive a cookie, allowing you to choose whether to accept it or not (for some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Customers who choose not to receive cookies probably cannot access those pages).

Vitale uses cookies to track your visit in ns. [sitowww.vitaleboutique.it.](http://www.vitaleboutique.it/) Our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer. This information does not identify you personally. You will therefore remain anonymous unless you have provided Vitale srl personal information in other forms.

Rights of the interested party.

According to alt 7 D. Lgs. 196/2003, the interested party has the right at any time to obtain from the data controller, or responsible if appointed, information concerning the processing of his data, about its methods and purpose and logic attached to it as well:

1)   confirmation of the existence of the data and their communication and their origin;

2)   the identity of the owner and managers as well as the subjects or categories of subjects to whom data may be communicated or who may become aware as managers or agents;

3)   updating, rectification or integration of the data;

4)   the cancellation, transformation into anonymous form or blocking of data processed unlawfully;

5)   certification that the operations referred to in points 3 and 4)) were brought to the attention of those to whom the data were communicated or disseminated, unless this requirement proves impossible or involves a manifestly disproportionate to the protected right;

6)   oppose: the processing of data, even if pertinent to the purpose of collection, for legitimate reasons; to the processing of data for commercial information purposes or for carrying out market research.

This can be done by writing to Vitale Srl at the following address:

Vitale, 68, 88900 Crotone Vitale Srl via Florence in the person of its legal representative pro-tempore Martino vital.

The data processing Titular is Vital, Vitale srl con sede in Via Florence 68, 88900 Crotone in the person of its legal representative and administrator Martin Vitale [info@vitaleboutique.it 0962 28609](mailto:info@vitaleboutique.it)

(In Accordance With ART. 13 D. LGS. 30.06.2003, n. 196)

In compliance with the provisions pursuant to the effects of the alt 13 D. Legislative Decree 30 June 2003 (personal data protection code) the vital, Vitale Srl, via Firenze 68.88900 Crotone, owner of the [website www.vitaleboutique.it, in its capacity as](http://www.vitaleboutique.it/) data controller, informs the person concerned on what the purposes and methods of processing of personal data collected, their scope of communication and dissemination, as well as the nature of their contribution.

I    processed data collected for the purpose of subscribing to the newsletter (specifically: email address, first and last name) will be processed and used for purposes directly instrumental to the fulfilment of the identification of the subjects that require receive site updates, in full compliance with the principles of fairness and necessity and applicable regulations.

II   processing of data is carried out through paper or electronic means and procedures ever, by persons authorized to do. The data are stored in computer files which are subject to the minimum security measures provided for by the legislator.

The personal data communicated by the Member are not subject to disclosure or communication.

The Subscriber can claim rights as expressed in articles. 7, 8, 9 and 10 of the D. Decree 30/06/03 of n. 196, covering the legal qualification of "Interested". These rights may be enforced by contacting the owner of the treatment or the vital, Vitale Srl in the person of its legal representative HOLDER according to the following and alternative modes: via e-mail at [info@vitaleboutique.it,](mailto:info@vitaleboutique.it) 0962 28609.0962 905744 telephone contacts, by postal mail to the address Vitale Srl Via Florence 68.88900 Crotone. In particular, under art. 7 the person concerned can obtain confirmation of the existence or not of personal data concerning him, even if not yet recorded, and their communication in intelligible form. Furthermore, the customer has the right to obtain information regarding: a the origin of personal data;) b) purposes and methods of processing; c) the logic applied in case of treatment with electronic instruments; d) the identity of the data controller, data processors and the representative appointed under article 5, paragraph 2 deH; e) subjects or categories of subjects to whom the personal data may be communicated or who may come to knowledge of it as designate representative in the territory of the State, managers or agents. The interested party has the right to obtain: a) the updating, rectification or, when interested, integration of data; b) cancellation, anonymization or blocking of data processed unlawfully, including data whose retention is unnecessary for the purposes for which the data were collected or subsequently processed; c) certification that the operations in letters a and b)) have been notified, as also related to their contents, to those to whom the data were communicated or disseminated, unless this requirement proves impossible or involves the use of means clearly disproportionate to the protected right. Finally, the interested party has the right to object, in whole or in part: a) for legitimate reasons the processing of personal data, pertinent for collection purposes; b) the processing of personal data concerning him for the purpose of sending advertising materials or direct selling or for carrying out market research or commercial communication.

I   user's data will be kept only for the period of enrollment. The cancellation from the newsletter will erase every given by the data controller.

II   consent to the processing of data is required to be subscribed to the newsletter and manifests itself with sending the registration request.

The titular that any missing or incorrect communication of the information necessary for submitting updates results in the impossibility for the titular to guarantee the fairness of the treatment itself.

The data processing Titular is Vitale Vitale srl, Via Firenze 68.88900 Crotone, in the person of its legal representative pro-tempore Martino Vital T 0962 28609 [info@vitaleboutique.it.](mailto:info@vitaleboutique.it)
